Please welcome the woman
leading La Familia into the future.
The Nation's Chairmom, Diana Aragon.
There was food poisoning
at our feeding program
in Corpuz City.
We're terminating our partnership,
effective immediately.
I need to get to the bottom of this!
Give me answers!
-Ms. D! Ms. D!
-Ms. D!
Code blue! Code blue!
What happened?
Why are you here?
You're not allowed in here.
-Uh…
-What happened?
-Who are you?
-Ouch!
What did you do to Ms. D?
Who are you?!
Patricia?!
Check the connections.
There's a loose connection.
-I'll fix it, doctor.
-Okay. Please secure it.
-Let me check.
-All good, doctor.
Who is it? Hold on!
Hold on!
Stop pounding the door!
What do you need?! Oh!
How may I help you?
Seriously?
You haven't paid the rent
for almost three months!
You keep asking for extensions!
You keep making empty promises!
Now, what? Still nothing!
Madam, of course, we'll pay the rent.
It's just that something
unexpected happened.
Maybe you can--
No! This is business, Carlota!
If you can't pay right now, then get out!
Maybe we can still talk about this.
Let's just wait for Patricia to come home.
She already emptied her savings!
-Martin, give our money back!
-Get out!
If you don't want
to get hurt, then pay up!
Where's our money?!
Vital signs are stable.
It's just a connection problem.
Argh! What the hell!
I told you I didn't do anything!
Patricia.
It's really you.
Patricia?
Let me just remind everyone
that I'm not just a board member here,
or a senior officer.
I'm the only…
family member right now.
La Familia exists because of our family.
And I have the same access,
same values, and principles.
And I have proven that
over the years of working here.
I agree.
The majority of the board
has already decided
to appoint Teodor Aragon
for the interim leadership position.
Well, thank you.
I better start working, then.
Meeting adjourned.
Hello, Georgia, my daughter.
Guess who's the new CEO?
Dad!
Something's happening here
in the hospital.
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
You really don't remember me?
I'm Enzo.
Lorenzo De Leon. Your childhood playmate.
Enzo?
-You work for Mom?
-Yes!
I'm her Chief of Staff.
But wait, what happened to you?
I haven't seen you for a long time.
I heard someone's pretending
to be my sister's daughter.
Where's that scammer?
She's not pretending, Sir Teddy.
What are you doing here?
Am I not supposed to be here?
Yes, but after all these years,
when Diana's in this condition,
now, you show up? What do you need? Money?
I heard your dad wasted everything he got
from the annulment.
He invested in all
these failed businesses.
-Did he tell you to come here?
-Don't drag Dad into this.
I just don't want Diana to be agitated.
What if she wakes up
and sees you first thing?
So, tell me.
How much do you need?
It's now or never!
Attorney, please explain it.
Well, legally speaking,
you're not entitled to any inheritance
while your mother is still alive.
-I know.
-So you do know?
If you're scaring me with your lawyer…
Article 777 of the Civil Code.
The right to inheritance
is only transferred
at the time of death of the heir.
As long as the parent is still alive,
they still have full ownership
of their assets.
However, as the only child,
I am the only one who has the right
to make decisions regarding her condition.
I have more right than you, Uncle Teddy.
I can even ban you from coming here.
Am I right, attorney?
I majored in Political Science.
Pre-law. I'm educated.
However, I am not an Aragon.
I am a Dela Cruz.
I won't involve myself in your mess.
But don't walk all over me
because we all know
I'm worth more than all of you.
That's it.
I am right. You're after the inheritance.
What kind of daughter are you?
Before you ask me
what kind of daughter I am,
why don't you ask her
what kind of mother she is?
-Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
-Why? Why?
My feet hurt.
I really thought
they were going to hurt us, Dad!
That might be the case
if we hadn't escaped!
Call Patricia.
Who knows what'll happen
if she comes home?
I've been trying to call her,
but she's not picking up!
Call her again!
Dad, where are we going to live?
Mom! Dad! Isn't this Patricia?
What is she doing there?
Jena, are you sure
this is the hospital Patricia went to?
Yes, I'm sure this is that hospital!
Oh? Aren't those reporters?
I'm sorry.
Is she still here?
Your sister's phone is still turned off.
We should split into groups,
-so we can find her quickly.
-All right, all right.
-I'll head in now.
-All right, sure. Sure.
We'll leave you two here.
Keep a close eye on our stuff.
-If something gets lost…
-Yes, Mom.
Bring it to the side. It's embarrassing!
You know what I think?
I think Diana Aragon's
in critical condition.
I mean, it's been hours, right?
And there's still nothing.
They don't even give updates
if she's still doing fine.
Rumors say her daughter showed up.
That's the story I want to know.
But she's lucky, isn't she?
She's the only child.
In other words,
she will inherit everything.
Dad.
Why didn't you tell me
where you were going?
You're not even picking up our calls!
If we hadn't seen you on the news,
we wouldn't have known where you are!
My phone died. I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
We were kicked out of the house.
They even swarmed us!
We can't go back there anymore.
Good thing I got your bag, Patricia.
At least I brought some of your clothes.
-Ow. Ow. Ow.
-Thank you.
-Dad? Are you all right?
-I'm fine. My legs just hurt.
-Mom.
-Oh?
I'm hungry, Mom.
-I want that.
-Me too, Mom. I'm hungry.
Mom, don't you have money?
Wait, let me check.
Oh, no, I don't think I have money left.
I-I'll handle it. I'll handle it.
-Come on.
-Can you walk?
-I can.
Yes, ma'am?
-What will you get?
-Uh, mister,
how much is the Japanese siomai with rice?
It's 50 pesos for one order, ma'am.
Fifty…
How many will you get?
-Four.
-Okay.
-Here it is.
-Thank you.
-Be careful.
-Thank you, Patricia!
Thank you!
-How generous.
-Where's the spoon?
You even treated us siomai and rice.
-Of course. Here, Dad.
-What about yours?
I'm full.
-Go eat.
-All right.
Miss.
Can I have some?
-Hey, hey!
-Wait, wait.
-Hey! Hey! Hey!
-Hey, wait! Hey!
-Dad, let it go.
-Patricia…
Are you okay? Did he hurt you?
It's dangerous for us
to be on the streets.
-Anyone home?
-Patricia.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
She's Patricia, Diana's daughter.
Daughter?
But ma'am never mentioned anything.
What's going on here?
-Nanny Cora.
-Patricia?
Patricia, is that you?
Cora.
Teach that man next time.
He doesn't know who he's talking to.
He lacks manners.
Uh, you'll have to excuse him.
Benjie wasn't here
when you were still here.
Uh, Benjie, he's Martin…
Ma'am Diana's ex-husband.
She's Carlota, the daughter
of a former maid here.
The Aragons funded her education,
and she worked in La Familia.
She's Diana's close friend!
Well, she used to be.
Now, Martin and Carlota are married.
You know them now, okay?
Your introduction's pretty good.
Oh! Hey.
Why'd you come here?
Uhm…
Nanny Cora, can we stay here?
We've got nowhere else to go.
But just for now. We won't be long.
Come in.
Wow! Are we going to live here now?
Let's go.
My gosh! This house is like a palace!
Palace?
It's more like a mausoleum.
You know, it's like
Diana completely forgot about you.
Didn't you notice?
You have no photos here. Not even one.
Patricia, you should settle down for now.
I'll make you something to eat.
Thank you.
Mom.
My gosh, Jena, you scared me.
But they said breakfast is ready!
What are you doing here, Mom?
Nothing, I'm just checking something.
Wow!
Mom! Wow!
Patricia's mom is so rich!
-But Mom…
-Hm?
Why didn't you tell us
Patricia's this rich?
We live in poverty
when she can just ask for help.
It's a long story, but the bottomline is…
-that woman's a jerk.
-Oh! Wow, a jerk, really?
Tell me. Have you ever thought
of leaving me?
-No!
-Exactly!
Imagine how bad of a mother she is
that her own child abandoned her!
You know, ever since Patricia left Diana,
not once did she ever
receive help from Diana.
Patricia's been through a lot.
We're still better because, at least…
you love me, right?
-You love me so much!
-Of course, Mom!
Wow! Mom! Ahh! Mom, oh, my gosh!
I only see this in celebrities' vlogs!
-Yes.
-T-These bags?
These cost millions!
I think this suits me. I really think so.
Wow!
Jena. Jena!
We now have a solution to our problems.
Where's the dress I bought for you?
Why are you wearing this?
It was itchy.
So this is why you keep failing.
All you do is watch TV.
Patricia.
My room's locked?
Your mom doesn't want it opened.
She probably uses it for storage.
-Patricia.
-It's fine.
I get it.
-I'm nothing to her.
-But you showed up.
You still visited her.
That means you still worry
about her, right?
I just checked to see
if I could get my inheritance.
That's what Uncle Teddy's accusing me of.
I know that's not true.
I believe your mother
still has a place in your heart.
I will never tire of praying
that you two will reconcile.
Your vitals look good and stable now.
There is no major neurological
damage or paralysis.
Can I be discharged now?
I need to get back to work.
Your body is still weak.
And as hospital protocol,
you have to be in a wheelchair
when you move around for one to two days.
You just suffered a heart attack.
We're not taking any chances.
I'll be back for the other test results.
Thanks, Doc.
Updates.
Due to the poisoning issue,
our stock price has dropped significantly.
Some supermarkets
also pulled out our products,
which has led to a decline in sales.
And the news coming out
aren't good either, Ms. D.
The victims?
We've paid for their hospitalization.
Some of them were easy to pacify
and talk to.
We're still talking to the rest of them.
Increase the financial help
to the victims.
This needs to be fixed now.
-Okay, ma'am.
-So…
Who's been in charge since I've been gone?
Sir Teddy was appointed as interim CEO.
Well, I'm awake now.
There's no need for that.
Anything else?
-Someone came to visit you.
-Who?
-The Grim Reaper?
-It's Patricia.
-Where is she?
-She left already.
It seems Patricia's life hasn't been easy.
She usually appears as a talent
in TV shows and movies.
On the side, she sells whatever she could.
Her father currently does not have a job.
Her stepmother earns a small wage
in her job at the city hall,
which is why Patricia is the breadwinner.
She pays for everything,
even her sisters' education.
-It's good that you've arrived.
-Good to see you're awake.
And you don't have to worry about anything
'cause I took care of everything
when you were sick.
What have you done about the poisoning?
Well, obviously, the crisis had
an impact on our brand.
Obviously.
Have you released
a public statement about that?
I mean, you're the head
of marketing, after all.
I'm glad you asked, uh…
We did. La Familia Corporation
official statement…
"La Familia Corporation
is aware of reports
after consuming Cala Soda products…"
Teddy. Teddy.
So many people are hospitalized
because of that.
But all you're going to say
is you're "aware of reports"?
How about, "We're deeply concerned,"
or "We sincerely apologize
to the victims and their families"?
-My gosh!
-You're right. We will revise.
You should have thought about that, right?
Did you see Patricia?
Did you kick her out?
She showed up after so many years, Diana.
She thought you were dying,
and she'd get the inheritance.
Well…
I'm awake, alert, and alive,
but I'm not very enthusiastic.
You know what I hate most?
It's when someone decides for me.
I'm the only one who can say
who's allowed and not allowed to visit me.
Ms. D…
-What's that now?
-You have to see this.
I have a surprise for you
because this is a once
in a lifetime moment!
These came from Italy!
The very first item I'll sell
is this red Dior!
It even smells like Italy!
But because I love you so, so much,
I'll sell this for only 20,000 pesos!
Item code is 001!
Just for 20,000 pesos--
Patricia, what are you doing?
-I'll fix that myself.
-No, it's fine. I can manage.
I'm really the one
who should be doing this.
I'm sorry we're being a bother.
But I used to do that for you.
Just think of what your mother would say.
Nanny Cora, I spent more time
with you when I was a child
than with my mother.
But let me take care of you now.
You know, in all honesty,
I've missed you so much.
Don't be too attached, okay?
I won't be here for long.
Besides, a lot of things
in my life have changed.
Diana?
Ms. D…
Watch your step.
Patricia.
So, you've been discharged.
How are you?
Diana?!
Oh.
You look like you've just seen a ghost.
I'm still alive, Carlota.
And you still haven't changed.
You're still digging through my trash.
Couldn't you wait
before you celebrate my death?
And did you really need
to do it in my house?
It wasn't Dad and Mom
who decided to come here.
It was me.
Is this how you raised our child, Martin?
A defender of wrongdoings.
An enabler of theft.
W-wait a minute.
We're not stealing anything from you.
She's trying to sell my stuff.
What are you talking about?
Mom!
I didn't know she'd wake up.
Besides, we're strapped for cash.
You're such a leech!
Ms. D, take it easy.
We'll take care of this.
Benjie, security, please.
-Hurry!
-Ah?
W-wait a minute! Wait a minute!
I'll give it back.
Now, shove it down your lungs!
-Take it to your grave!
-That's enough.
Who do you think you are?
You're not even a good wife,
much less a good mother!
-Mom, stop it.
-What are you going to do?
You're no better than us, Diana.
Sure, you're surrounded
by all these nice things,
but we all know that you're alone.
You're all alone now
because no one can stand you!
-Please, stop it.
-Right?
-Come at me!
-Security, get them out please.
Ma'am…
No, I'm not leaving.
-I'm not leaving!
-Mom!
-I said, I'm not leaving!
-Mom, stop!
That's enough.
Let my mother go!
-Mom, that's enough!
-Come with us!
-Stop it!
-Dad!
That's enough!
Enough!
Come on, let's get you up.
You don't need to drag us out.
I wouldn't even come here
if I had somewhere else to go!
I just thought you've changed.
But I thought wrong.
But that's on me. I should've known.
Like when I asked for your help when…
when I needed a mother,
you just let Dad get injured!
Do you really think
I'm a bad person?
Well, that's what you're showing me.
When Dad got into an accident,
Mommy Carlota was there for us.
So, you're defending a thief?
All right.
Call the cops.
But all I want…
is that you put me in jail instead.
Not my mother.
I want you to never touch my family again.
You two.
You got what you wanted.
For the love of God, leave.
Please, leave.
Ms. D, take it easy.
Should I still call the police?
No.
Patricia left it behind.
Why did you let them all in?
Because they needed help.
Diana,
Patricia is still your daughter.
You think she still sees me as her mom?
How long are you going to let this on?
If you didn't have problems
in La Familia before,
it wouldn't have ended up this way.
You're always away!
Not just that, Sir Lucio.
There are missing funds.
It's possible that there's
a conspiracy in the company.
WHERE ARE YOU? PATRICIA'S LOOKING FOR YOU.
PATRICIA'S PERFORMING NEXT.
CAN YOU MAKE IT?
THE PROGRAM'S ALMOST OVER.
Diana, we have urgent business here.
Uh…
I'm sorry, Dad.
Patricia has a school event today.
We're facing a crisis in the company.
We're losing millions of pesos.
And you're worried about that?
Why?
Will that be Patricia's
last school performance?
Will she die if you don't come?
I promised her, Dad.
People's jobs depend on us.
And you're risking all that
just to go to a school program?
Well then, if you want, leave!
And make sure to bring all of your stuff
because you're not
coming back here anymore.
What else do you want me to do?
Don't you have
any other necklace that isn't tacky?
Dad, what more do you want from me?
When you asked me to choose
between you and Martin,
I chose Martin because
we were building a family.
But you asked me to come back
because you don't trust Teddy.
So, that's how you see it?
You don't see it as you, making a mistake
and I, forgiving you and letting you back?
Is loving a mistake?
Is choosing my family a mistake?
This is not just because of the company.
It's because you deserve
so much more better.
Do you think you'll be happy
and content with life as a housewife?
You're just wasting
your skills and intellect
on a man that isn't even on your level.
My god, Diana!
Admit it.
If that man didn't get you pregnant,
you wouldn't even marry him.
I'm telling the truth!
You are thieves!
How can I trust you with the company
if you keep messing up like this?
Huh?
I let you organize an event,
and what happened?
It was a failure!
Can't you make a good decision for once?
First, that husband of yours.
You married a born loser!
Just accept it, Dad.
Martin is my husband and we have a child.
Just let me know if you can't do it,
and let's burn La Familia to the ground!
Instead of marrying an honorable man,
you chose a lowly employee of La Familia.
You chose an idiot!
My Dad is not an idiot!
-Patricia.
-I can call your father
whatever I want.
You're an Aragon.
Learn to act like one.
Patricia, please wait outside.
Patricia.
Did you see that?
Your daughter already learned
how to talk back to me!
She's just defending her father.
She's not your employee or a board member.
I won't let you treat her
the way you treat me.
Dad.
Whatever disappointment you have in me,
don't pass it on to my daughter.
I will fix what happened tonight.
But when it comes to my child,
I call the shots, Dad.
I may not be the ideal father to you.
But don't ever forget.
Every time I was hard on you,
it's because I know
you have what it takes.
It's a cruel world out there!
I treat you like this to strengthen you.
Diana.
You are meant to lead La Familia.
This is our legacy.
Promise me.
Promise me, you will stay strong.
Promise me you won't let La Familia down.
Dad!
Ma'am.
Give me an update.
Ten people died, all factory employees.
Two were injured.
Sir Lucio and…
Cecilia Pineda.
We're just waiting for her to wake up.
We've also informed her family.
What was Dad doing in the factory?
The clients are breathing down our necks
ever since production stopped.
The banks are following up as well.
What did our insurance say?
We have to rebuild as soon as possible.
I'm waiting for the final report
from the fire protection
to confirm if it was
a case of arson or not.
Ma'am.
Why do you have this?
Did you light it inside the factory?
Patricia, tell me! What did you do?
Are you sure?
Did he really say that?
Yes, sir.
I heard Grandpa say it.
"Let's burn La Familia to the ground."
Excuse me? Who are you?
We're police investigators, ma'am.
We just have some follow-up
questions about the fire.
And I am the insurance investigator
who handles the property claim.
Why are you interrogating my daughter?
We need to look at every angle.
And your daughter
happened to be in the scene.
But you don't have permission.
She's just a child.
I let them in, Diana.
They were just asking questions.
And I'm here to supervise.
Patricia, why did you say that?
Why did you say that?
I just said what I heard Grandpa say.
You ruined everything!
Go home. I'll call the driver.
-But, Mom…
-Patricia!
For once, would you listen to me?
You don't understand!
You have no idea what a huge mess this is!
Go home!
Code blue!
-Excuse me.
-Dad…
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
You need to stay out here.
No heartbeat. Start compression.
Time of death: 5:17 p.m.
Dad…
Dad!
No… No, Dad.
Diana, stop it!
-That's enough!
-Let me go, you bastard!
-You bastard!
You traitor! And you!
I thought you were my friend!
I treated you as family!
How could you do this to me?!
-Diana, that's enough!
-You left him!
I was the only one there to catch him.
You can't always be the lucky one, Diana.
You think you can always get
anything you want?
Why? Because you're rich, huh?!
Diana!
Our marriage has been struggling
for a long time!
We have a child.
Did you even think about her, huh?!
You didn't even think about her!
You don't deserve me!
No!
Do you want to be
with your mom or your dad?
I want to be with Dad.
Diana?
Wait. What are you doing here?
Our marriage has been annulled.
Don't make a scene.
I separated with you,
but not with my daughter.
If I lose my patience,
I'm going to send you to jail.
Wait.
Don't send Dad to jail!
Patricia.
Enough, okay?
You've already proven your point.
Let's go home, dear.
Are you going to make it hard for the kid?
I let you meet her freely.
That's why I agreed to visitation rights.
Why do you have to take
my daughter away from me?
Because she chose to be with me.
What? Do you think I'm having fun at work?
I'm doing this for her future.
I'm doing this for your future.
Future? If we go home,
are you going to finally be a mother?
Are you going to start loving me?
Or will you still blame me
for what happened to Grandpa?
You don't know what you're talking about.
I don't want to go with you!
Is the annulment settlement
not enough for you?
I've given you everything you asked for,
but that doesn't include my daughter.
I am going to file for sole custody.
Do it.
See you in court.
Let's go.
Martin poisoned Patricia's heart
a long time ago.
I understand how you feel.
I understand Patricia as well.
I know you both have
unresolved issues with each other.
Patricia was the one who decided
to cut me off from her life.
When does motherhood end?
I did fine on my own.
If she doesn't need me anymore,
then I won't need her either.
But…
are you happy?
Happy?
I took the entire La Familia
out of the ashes.
And if Patricia thinks
that makes me
the worst person in the world,
there's nothing I can do about it.
I can accept that she doesn't
care about me anymore.
If you can only go back--
We can't go back
to the way things were, Nanny Cora.
But I believe…
that there is a reason…
why you two met again.
There…
I'm glad you picked up last night.
I have no one else to call.
Don't worry about it.
I usually sleep late.
-Bestie.
-Hmm?
You can borrow and use this for now.
Okay. Thank you.
-This way. Careful.
-No problem.
Thankfully, my aunt had
a place available for tenants.
That means we can now go
to auditions together.
Mm. You're right.
Oh, thank you.
Did you receive a text?
They're looking for talents today.
Yes. Do you want to go together?
-I'll just go to the restroom.
-Mm.
Okay.
Patricia.
Thank you.
Because you're still thinking about us.
Just remember…
you're all my responsibility.
I will never abandon you.
Thank you, Patricia.
Uh, Patricia.
I think working as a talent
won't suffice now.
Looks like you need to find a regular job.
Our living cost is increasing.
My salary can't cover all of it.
Don't worry.
Once I open a business and hit it big,
you won't have to work.
-Bestie, are you ready?
-Mm-hmm. Let's go.
Wait. Let me walk you out.
Okay.
-Take care, okay?
-We will.
-We'll go now.
-Stay safe.
April, you take care of that.
It's so annoying!
We were already in a mansion.
Why do we have to go back
to something like this? Gosh!
You know, Jena, this is better
than having no house at all.
I'm still mad about what
Patricia's mom did to us.
It's really unfortunate.
My pictures turned out great.
Only if I could post them.
I get so annoyed
every time I see Ms. Diana's face here.
See her face? What?
Here, Mom.
I was able to film what she did to us.
Look.
We've already reached
settlement with some of the victims.
Others need a little more convincing,
but I'm confident
that we'll overcome this.
What I want is for us to move forward.
I'm already setting
a meeting with Burger City
to fix what happened.
Excuse me. That's good,
but it looks like we have
another PR nightmare.
What are you talking about?
Georgia just sent this to me.
It's trending on social media,
and it's about you
and Patricia's family.
April, stop.
That's enough!
-Guards, that's enough!
-Enough of this!
You two.
You got what you wanted.
"Is that supposed to be the chairmom?
-More like chairmonster."
-Enough.
"That's why her daughter
refuses to see her…"
-I said enough.
-"What…"
I'm sorry. I'm just reading the comments.
For decades, the image of La Familia
is "always together with the family"
and "the silent member of the family."
This will affect the brand.
Who's going to believe in our brand now?
You know how people are.
They don't like fighting
with your own flesh and blood.
Our stocks are being monitored.
If we don't control this right away--
La Familia has been through worse.
Much worse than just a stupid viral video.
I suggest everyone remember that
before you panic like amateurs.
You know our bylaws, Diana.
If the value of our shares drops by 30%,
the poison pill clause will take effect.
You're going to dilute my shares?
There's already a talk, internally.
It's about leadership stability.
If this keeps happening…
If public confidence keeps dropping,
I think we may have
to change the leadership.
Ah.
So all of this boils down to that?
One incident and you're already
discussing replacement.
Let me be clear.
La Familia will stabilize.
The company will recover.
And when that happens,
I expect every single person
in this room, questioning me…
and those who are quick to forget
to remember that I…
kept La Familia standing.
Meeting adjourned.
Ungrateful fools!
Hey, are you okay?
I'm fine.
You know,
I think you should hear them out.
Hear them out?
After everything I have done
for this company?
Look, I'm not saying that you're wrong.
But… but they're not totally wrong.
I'm sorry, Teddy.
But you're the last person
I'll ask for advice.
You know, you and Dad…
You're totally alike.
Your world revolves around this company.
You've sold your soul for this company.
Are you conspiring with them, Teddy?
What are you talking about?
-I'm on your side. I'm your brother.
-Oh, cut the crap!
I'm sorry that your dream
to replace me didn't come true.
-Oh, come on, Diana.
-Isn't it true?
You wanted to do that
since you went back home, right?
After Dad died,
you took your inheritance
because you said you wanted
to start on your own.
But what happened? You came back.
Because you failed.
I will never allow you
to do that to La Familia.
I am La Familia.
I will not let you ruin this company.
But, Mom, that was wrong.
I'm in the wrong again.
Why are you…
taking Diana's side?
Oh, well…
She's the one who gave birth to you.
Who am I compared to her?
I'm the one who raised you.
I'm not taking her side.
I'm just saying
that you did the wrong thing.
Her giving birth to me
has nothing to do with this.
You shouldn't have spread the video.
People need to feel
that La Familia is still the brand
that they grew up with.
Let's go back to the emotional roots.
Family values.
Warmth.
-Unity.
-No, no. Joey, stop.
Diana, is there a problem?
Yes, Joey.
It's safe, predictable.
It's like a Christmas
or Valentine's Day campaign.
-Diana.
-It's same old, same old.
I don't know anything!
You're accusing me of the wrong thing!
You don't know anything?!
Take this!
Hold! Hold!
Okay. Double, out. Bianca, go!
Double, out!
Ah, wait! Cut, cut!
-Let's do it again.
-Again?
So, Chairmom Diana,
we plan to rebuild trust
through sincerity.
As you can see…
-Next!
-Action!
I don't know anything!
You're accusing me of the wrong thing!
You don't know anything?!
Take this!
Hold! Okay. Out, double! Bianca, go!
I propose that we launch
with a major apology campaign.
Pathetic. Next!
-Ah!
-Next!
-Damn you!
You damn witch!
Hold! Out! Double, out! Bianca, in!
From your line, Bianca, okay?
Stop!
I didn't steal anything from you!
He was in love with me first!
Cut! Good take, actors!
Very good, very good.
This is so frustrating.
I know, Ms. D.
Look, we still have one last pitch.
Well, send them in.
And you are?
Ricardo Salvador.
PR consultant. Crisis Management Expert.
I've worked with politicians,
celebrities, corporations.
And Silver Graph Hall of Famer.
What agency is he from?
Ms. D, it doesn't seem
like he has an agency.
I'm independent.
I represent myself.
So, what's your advertising campaign?
That's your first mistake.
Excuse me?
You see it as an advertising issue.
Your problem is an image crisis.
Diana, your problem is…
You're lying too much.
For decades, you've shown
that a family is perfect
as long as they have
Cala Soda on their table.
You portray La Familia
as something perfect.
That's why you called yourself
the chairmom.
That's not real, Diana.
You have to show the truth.
A family can be messy.
Sometimes they fight,
scream at each other,
or hurt each other.
But at the end of the day,
they are still a family.
What commercial do you have in mind?
You don't need
another fake smiling campaign.
What you need…
is a tell-all sit-down interview.
Interview?
People think they know your story.
So…
Give them your own version
before somebody else does.
And you think that should fix everything?
Of course not.
But it changes the conversation.
Diana.
Right now, people see you as someone…
untouchable.
People are no longer
interested in perfection.
What they need to see
is authenticity.
And trust me.
Your family…
is very, very marketable.
Thank you, Mr. Salvador, for your time.
-Enzo.
-Ms. D.
Find out everything
about that Ricardo Salvador.
Check if his credentials are real.
I'd like to know…
why he would be
so interested in this mess.
What are you waiting for?
Cala Soda just dropped to number two.
It's the first time in years.
What?
Our distributors canceled their orders.
Grocery stores and convenience stores
are losing sales.
Also, there's an increasing call
on social media
for consumers to boycott our products.
-Shut up! Get out!
-Okay, ma'am.
Ms. D, the background check is complete.
Proceed.
Ricardo Salvador.
He studied at a top-notch university
in Indonesia,
and graduated at the top of his class.
He's also a Silver Graph
Awards Hall of Famer.
He was telling the truth.
He is known
as one of the best crisis doctors.
For instance, a politician from Indonesia
who was involved
in a major corruption scandal
got reelected with his help.
He also turned
a tech company's data breach
into an innovation story.
And he changed the image of a celebrity
accused of drug abuse to a survivor.
He's an expert in manipulating
public perception, Ms. D.
Why did he go back to the Philippines?
He wanted to do his own thing.
He's establishing his practice here.
Set a meeting with him.
You stole my husband!
You deserve more than this!
Cut!
Good take!
-Okay. Reset.
-Are you okay? Okay.
We'll shoot at a different angle
to be sure.
I have to submerge my face in water again?
-You're the body double, right?
-Yes.
Have the makeup department fix your look
-to ensure continuity.
-Okay.
-Kaori, just keep it up.
-Safety first, right?
-Of course. I know.
-Just add more intensity.
-I love my life.
-Are you okay?
-Okay.
-Andi, come here.
-Sit down first.
Take care.
Make it more intense, okay?
Can you try this? Are you okay with…
Patricia.
Sir.
I'm flattered that you know my name.
Are you the producer?
No.
I'm Ricardo Salvador.
I'm La Familia's new PR specialist.
I have an offer for you.
I just need your cooperation.
I don't want to have
any connection with my mom
and you expect me to cooperate?
You're drowning in debt.
You need money
to settle your father's mess.
We'll pay you so you can start over.
I take it that it comes at a cost.
Just like everything else in life.
But I can assure you one thing.
It'll be easier than doing all this.
Here's my calling card.
Think about it.
It's the perfect role for you.
What's the real story
behind one of the country's
richest families?
According to an initial report,
Diana Aragon suffered a heart attack
after there was
a reported issue of food poisoning
in one of their feeding programs.
-You deserve more than this!
-Take this!
-Dad!
-Ah!
Get out of here!
For the first time ever,
the mother and daughter
everyone is talking about
will face each other.
This Sunday,
let's break the silence.
It's the exclusive interview
everyone is waiting for.
Diana Aragon.
Patricia Aragon Dela Cruz.
Mother and daughter.
They will face and confront each other
in a tell-all interview.
This Sunday on…
Uncovered!
Ms. D? Patricia?
The interview is about to start.
Coming.
All good now, Ms. D.
She's still an Aragon.
I have to keep an eye on her.
I have it from good sources
that Patricia will be working
at La Familia.
Working at La Familia
wasn't part of the deal.
It's not just Diana
who'll benefit from this.
It will also change your life.
-No excuses.
-Ah!
-Can you handle it?
-Of course.
Why are you meddling with something
that's not within your scope of work?
Why are you yelling at my daughter?
I'm scolding her
because she did something wrong.
Just admit that you're mad at Patricia.
You still see me that way even until now?